Vinh Huynh

ABOUT ME

I'm a developer with an art & design background in gaming. I am well-versed in the languages of the web and enjoy finding creative solutions to an array of challenges. My design sensibilities allow me to unite function & form effectively and create outstanding user experiences.

LINKEDIN

www.linkedin.com/in/vinh-huynh

PORTFOLIO

www.vinh512.github.io

GITHUR

www.github.com/Vinh512

SKILLS

Javascript	jQuery	Node.js	Firebase	Photoshop
HTML	Bootstrap	Express	Git / GitHub	Illustrator
CSS	React	MongoDB	RESTful API	3DS Max

PROJECTS

Paper, Pencil, Scissors - A platform for teachers to request classroom supplies from generous donors. Worked with a team of developers and UI/UX designers to implement the designers' visions and functionality. Used an Amazon node module to make AJAX calls to retrieve product data.

Peer Pulse - An app that facilitates decision-making allowing users to submit and vote for activities in which the most-voted result is chosen. Worked on a team of developers using React and Firebase.

EXPERIENCE

KingsIsle Entertainment - Environment Artist

June 2011 - May 2016

- Worked on the highly successful Wizards 101 and Pirate 101
- Designed and created various art assets & environments

Sony Computer Entertainment America - Scan Artist Contractor

Feb 2010 - April 2011

- Optimized and aligned 3D head scans
- Used sculpting software to refine end product

Incinerator Studios - Environment Artist

Sept 2007 - July 2009

- Worked on various PS2 and Wii titles based on popular IPs
- Modeled, unwrapped, and textured art assets & envrionments

EDUCATION

General Assembly Austin - Web Development Immersive

Feb 2017

The Art Institute San Diego - Game Art & Design

Dec 2005